Watch on kissasia.li
[Road to Success]
[Episode 3]
How did you defend it?
-How are you holding up?
-Where were you?
Here.
Have some water.
Thank you, Ms. Lin.
Good job, everyone.
Do you want to
share your thoughts?
I'll go first.
-Idiot referee!
-Wait! Are you out of your mind?
You missed your chance.
Next.
I really didn't realize
my hand had touched the ball.
You didn't touch it at all.
That referee is blind.
It was a borderline call.
Why give them a penalty?
Forget it.
They always call it against
small teams like us.
I told you.
We shouldn't have come here
just to get humiliated.
Ms. Lin,
who is this guy next to you?
I forgot to introduce him.
He's my primary school classmate
who just came back from abroad.
He's a professional football coach.
Make your lies somewhat logical.
Do you know how hard it is
to get a coaching license abroad?
Miss, he's trying to hit on you, right?
Don't call him out.
Yes.
-He's not even pretending anymore.
-What did I say?
I mean
getting a football coaching license abroad
is indeed difficult.
Why would a professional football coach
who just came back from abroad
come to watch our school football game?
Don't you find it boring?
Yeah.
Not at all.
I think every football match
is very interesting.
Any other questions?
If you are a coach,
are you the kind who coaches kids?
I used to coach a youth team.
Now I'm unemployed.
Youth team?
Which lousy club?
Nanton.
Impossible.
Do you know
where Nanton Youth Team stands in Europe?
Well then,
tell me.
Last year in the European Youth League,
how many points did Nanton get
in the first stage of the first season?
What was their ranking?
Do you know?
Can't I test him?
First place.
First stage,
8 matches,
20 points.
Then who did they play in the last match
and what was the score?
If you're so good,
why did you come back?
I don't mind
telling you stories
for the whole second half.
But my primary school classmate
might mind.
That's right.
I asked him here
to teach you guys
some football tactics for the second half.
Isn't this just a formality?
Do we really need tactics?
Right.
Our problem right now is,
firstly, our stamina may not hold up.
Secondly,
our morale is low,
and their attack is really strong.
We probably won't be able to
hold them off in the second half.
Do you have any suggestions?
Your opponent, Ning'an,
is nicknamed the Cheetah.
As the name implies,
they are fast,
but they also have a weakness.
Who doesn't know that?
They have weak endurance.
Right.
But your endurance is even worse.
You guys haven't trained
in a long time, right?
Qin Ao.
Any suggestions?
If you want to win,
just listen to me.
It feels like
he's speaking in professional terms.
But when he puts them all together,
I can't understand a thing.
This guy
is really weird.
Why did he suddenly appear at my house,
and then suddenly appear here?
Is it really
just a coincidence?
Never mind.
I'll focus on the match first.
Those who want to hear the tactics,
come here.
Lin Lu, hurry.
-Come here, everyone.
-Let's just listen.
There's no harm anyway.
Let's go.
Fu.
Come on, defenders, raise your hands.
You three start from here.
Although the curling shots...
I'm so sleepy.
Are a bit hard for you now.
I hope this QR Code is reliable
and can actually be useful.
Of course.
If the forwards are making a run
in the same direction,
a driven pass will do.
That simple?
Wouldn't that be easy to defend against?
In football,
there are many complex tactics,
but there is only one
that is the simplest.
Which one?
Always stay focused.
Your focus should always
be on the ball.
Elevating tactics
to a philosophical level—
he sure can talk.
Ms. Lin,
be careful not to get tricked.
I'm also worried.
You're going to lose anyway.
Why not give it a try?
That makes sense.
We're here to have fun anyway.
Just be happy.
Come on!
[Yongchuan Provincial Youth Super League]
-Come on!
[Hongjing No. 8 High School vs.
Ning'an Experimental School]
Do you want to try
that method?
What are you thinking?
It's impossible for a Chinese person
to coach a European football club.
If what he said is true,
I could play
in one of Europe's top five leagues.
He's a fraud.
The second half begins.
The teams switch sides.
Ning'an Experimental School
is still in the lead.
2-0.
Ning'an Experimental School still
still leads 2-0.
Hongjing No. 8 High School's attack
is intercepted again.
Counterattack!
Ning'an Experimental School
breaks into the penalty area—
a shot from a tight angle!
Feng Suo!
He saved the ball!
They all say your method is unreliable.
Will it work?
Indeed.
A normal coach
wouldn't set it up this way.
But I'm no normal coach.
How would
a normal coach set it up then?
They would have them
play mid-block defense first,
draw the opponent's attack,
and then launch a counterattack.
Then why didn't you?
We're already behind anyway.
We might as well go all out.
More importantly,
I can't let your money go to waste.
After all, I'm worth it.
Boss, I really can't run anymore.
I feel like I'll drop dead
if I keep running.
Slow down. Don't get hurt.
Take it easy.
Alright.
Why is the opponent obviously exhausted
but still trying so hard?
Because you are too weak,
and they want to score more goals.
So cunning.
The goalkeeper
of Hongjing No. 8 High School
throws the ball to No. 6 Lin Lu.
Lin Lu passes to No. 10 Fu Xinshu.
Try a long pass from the backfield
to find the forward.
Just rely on the forward's
precise first touch.
Qin Ao, Chen Jianghe!
-Let's try it.
-A long pass!
It's actually a long pass tactic!
The pass goes over
Ning'an Experimental School's defense line
and reaches the forward!
Qin Ao!
They're very fast!
This ball is passed to Chen Jianghe!
Chen Jianghe shoots!
What a pity. The shot is blocked.
Although it didn't go in,
this is the first time
we've seen effective teamwork from
-Hongjing No. 8 High School, come on!
-Hongjing No. 8 High School! What happened just now?
Their form
has obviously improved.
It's impossible
for a Chinese person to coach
a European football club.
Wide.
If what he said is true,
I could play
in one of Europe's top five leagues.
Too high.
It's over.
It's a mess.
Can you stop talking?
[78']
It's the 78th minute of the match.
Hongjing No. 8 High School
has a corner kick,
taken by No. 6, Lin Lu.
The ball is passed to No. 9, Qin Ao.
Qin Ao fails to win the header.
Hongjing No. 8 High School
no longer has the advantage in the air.
Possession goes to
Ning'an Experimental School.
No. 14 and No. 13
[Yongchuan Provincial Youth Super League]
are linking up.
[Hongjing No. 8 High School vs.
Ning'an Experimental School]
And shoot!
The ball is saved by
Hongjing No. 8 High School's goalkeeper.
Their players
are better built than our forwards.
So normally,
when you fight for the ball,
you have no advantage.
You need to be flexible
and avoid direct confrontation.
Don't rely on your height in aerial duels.
Keep your eyes on the landing point
and compete for the second ball.
We can see Qin Ao
from Hongjing No. 8 High School
no longer going for aerial duels
like before,
but instead moving to the landing point
to compete for the second ball.
Let's trust him for now!
It's a brilliant decision!
He successfully intercepts the ball.
How did Hongjing No. 8 High School
suddenly come up with this?
Their new tactic is really impressive!
It's a goal!
-Well done!
-Congratulations to Hongjing No. 8 High School for pulling one back!
The score is now 2-1.
[Ning'an Experimental School 2–0
Hongjing No. 8 High School]
Qin Ao!
Nice shot!
Bro!
-The match is almost over.
-Well done!
-One more!
-Let's go! One more goal!
Such a goal is impossible to replicate.
It not only helps them pull one back,
but more importantly,
it helps the whole team
regain confidence.
Keep trying to win possession.
Play long balls up to the forwards.
This QR Code
really knows his stuff.
[Yongchuan Provincial Youth Super League]
Three minutes of stoppage time
in the second half.
[Hongjing No. 8 High School vs.
Ning'an Experimental School]
The current score is 2-1.
Ning'an Experimental School
is in the lead.
Players from both sides
are giving it their all.
In the final moments,
will Hongjing No. 8 High School equalize,
or will Ning'an Experimental School
win the game?
Fu!
Ning'an Experimental School's corner kick—
let's see who wins the second ball.
No. 12, Chen Weidong,
intercepted the ball.
He might be offside!
All their players
are too close to our half.
This forces our forwards
to move back with them.
It's easy to fall into an offside trap.
Our space is too small.
They are setting an offside trap.
Can't you beat the offside trap?
Because of your frequent attacks,
their defenders are reaching their limit.
Especially the right-back.
He's slow to turn to his left.
Play down his left side.
Fall back and defend!
They beat the offside trap!
What an amazing decision!
Would their defenders make such a mistake?
They completely changed!
They're showing
why they were once runners-up!
If you are lucky enough.
A goal!
My God! In stoppage time!
We didn't lose!
It's a last-minute equalizer
to make it 2–2!
Bravo!
We didn't lose!
Good shot!
♪ Who isn't going through nights
of darkness and confusion ♪
♪ Stumbling, covered in wounds,
losing direction ♪
♪ Wandering alone,
gaining strength through pain ♪
Thank you
for helping them turn the tide.
No need.
♪ Riding the wind,
chasing an unknown horizon ♪
You paid for it.
I can see
♪ Looking up,
dreaming side by side of great ideals ♪
that they didn't really want to lose.
They were just afraid of losing face.
♪ The vast world
awaits youth to arrive ♪
♪ If braving the wind and waves ♪
♪ Can be called growth ♪
He just left?
♪ I will stubbornly
go against the current ♪
♪ And run wild once ♪
How rude.
♪ Even if the road ahead is long ♪
If you don't try your best,
♪ I will still be unstoppable ♪
luck won't favor you.
♪ Break through all confusion ♪
♪ Chase my own light ♪
♪ In the storm I grow resilient wings ♪
♪ Even if no one is clapping ♪
-You practiced in secret?
-Amazing, right?
♪ I will still fight my way forward ♪
Just that one shot.
Awesome, bro.
You've definitely been practicing
in secret.
Awesome.
What are you doing?
You must be Ms. Lin
from the P.E. department.
I'm Director Jin.
The chemistry competition just ended.
Their bus happens to be broken.
They have to rush back
for a post-competition review.
Let us borrow your bus.
Director Jin,
this is our football team's car.
If your car is broken,
how about we squeeze in together?
But...
There are only so many seats.
I'm afraid we won't fit.
The academic teachers are still waiting
at school.
You guys on the team,
please do me a favor.
Thank you.
I'll have the bus come back
to pick you up later.
Aren't we in a hurry too?
Mr. Jin is the most biased teacher.
We're all tired after the match too.
He didn't even pretend to care.
He kicked the ladder away
after climbing up.
Ms. Lin,
what should we do?
I don't know.
I'm new here too.
How about
I treat you to something nice to eat?
Ms. Lin,
I know a really good
stir-fry restaurant nearby.
But... it's a bit expensive.
It doesn't matter.
As long as you're happy.
Where is it?
Over there.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
How did you get in?
The door downstairs was wide open.
And your own door was unlocked.
Stop looking so miserable.
Look what I brought you.
Doesn't it make the place feel more alive?
It's okay.
Store them yourself.
Just okay?
How would you survive without me?
Wi-Fi, Wi-Fi, Wi-Fi.
Wang Fa.
Why
isn't the password
on the back of the router?
The password is 8 eights.
Internet isn't that expensive.
Eight eights?
Change it.
That's too easy to guess.
Anyone can connect.
Alright, connected.
Sharing the same network makes us family.
Who's your family?
Did my sister say yes to you?
Watch your mouth.
Once I, Yu Bo, am your agent,
I'm your agent for life.
Of course we're family.
Your new house is...
Who's calling at this hour?
Hello?
How did the interview go?
Really?
That's great.
Yes.
I also think I'm indeed
the best fit for Yongchuan Hengjiu.
Okay.
I got it.
Bye.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
My lifelong agent
is running away now?
I'm going to Yongchuan Hengjiu.
Yongchuan
is the closest place to your sister.
Let me borrow a suit of yours.
I need to look the part.
[Studied in the UK] [Psychology major]
[Likes spicy food] [Hates coriander]
[Not good at sports] [Can't ride a bike]
[Hates rainy days]
[Spade Q, Lin Wanxing]
Did you come all the way to Hongjing
just to investigate Lin Wanxing?
Yes.
Lin Wanxing
is my landlady now.
She lives downstairs.
Okay.
-This hits the spot.
-7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
Nothing like an iced tea after a match.
If we hadn't run into Jin Laoyao today,
it would've been perfect.
It's not the first time
we've been despised.
Aren't you used to it by now?
True.
A lousy football team
means nothing.
Guys,
don't come to me
for this kind of thing again.
It's too annoying.
Don't say that.
We got our special admission spots
because we played football.
Yeah.
Even though we only came in second place
in the junior high regional finals,
didn't Jiang still let us
get special admission
to Hongjing No. 8 High School?
Back then,
we were all in one talent class.
That was great.
So what?
Didn't he abandon us in the end?
Exactly.
When the talent class was disbanded,
did anyone ask for our opinion?
We made a fuss
at the Academic Affairs Office with Qin,
and almost got a demerit, right?
We all ended up as transfer students
and were looked down on wherever we went.
Don't tell me you've all forgotten.
And that Jiang Tianyu.
If he hadn't left,
would we have been disbanded
in our freshman year?
How many orders of
salted egg yolk chicken wings do you want?
Are 2 enough?
That's not enough.
We need at least 4.
You guys order.
I'm telling you.
I want the shredded potatoes.
-I want bullfrog.
-And braised pork.
You're too slow.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Too slow.
Do you want braised pork?
Yes, two orders.
-Stir-fried beef.
-You guys keep ordering.
Three orders.
Just order 2.
-Duck claws.
-Let's get more. 3 orders.
Spicy soft-shelled turtle.
Yes.
Cabbage...
Since there are so many of us,
get 3 orders.
Sure.
Ms. Lin, what do you want to eat?
Let me see.
Okay.
By the way, Ms. Lin,
we won today all thanks to your
elementary school classmate.
Why didn't you invite him to eat with us?
It was just a chance encounter.
No need for that.
Ms. Lin,
he said he was the former coach of Nanton.
Is that true?
Bro,
if he's the former Nanton coach,
I'm Mbappé.
Then I'm Yamal.
If you don't believe me,
I'll check right now
and expose this liar.
[Winfred Wang] [Nanton Fan Forum]
[Winfred Wang]
Oh my. Come on.
Wait. Is it really him?
-What?
-Mr. Win.
Is it really him?
-It's really him.
-It's really him?
-I remember him.
-Is it really him?
Mr. Win.
-Hello, excuse me. The food is here.
-The food is here.
-Who cares which team he coaches?
-It's really him.
I'm hungry anyway.
I'll eat first.
Here, Ms. Lin.
Thank you.
By the way, Fu,
the thing you mentioned before—
the weird thing you received—
should you tell me what it is now?
There's nothing.
What?
I didn't receive anything.
I lied.
I just wanted us
to play football together.
Fu,
you really want to play football
that much?
What was there to look forward to
in a game we were bound to lose?
Was it necessary for you to do this?
It's fine.
Just treat it as a free autumn trip.
And we got a free meal out of it, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Thank you, Ms. Lin.
-Thank you, Ms. Lin.
By the way,
this game is a draw.
Are we going to keep playing?
Keep playing?
Why bother?
They dribbled past us
like we weren't even there.
Have some awareness, bro.
We're just a bunch of losers.
We should just hide in the corner.
Why dream of shining?
Anyway,
we accomplished our mission honorably.
It's good to quit while we're ahead,
isn't it?
Yeah, we don't even have a full team.
Come on.
To our honorable retirement.
-Come on.
-Cheers to losers.
-Cheers!
Cheers!
This is really delicious.
It's really delicious.
You eat this.
I want to eat that.
I want to eat this.
This one is a bit salty.
-This is quite good.
-This is not bad.
I'm so full.
Really stuffed.
Thank you, Ms. Lin,
for treating us to this meal.
Thank you, Ms. Lin.
You're welcome.
Do you really like playing football?
Then why don't you look happy?
Isn't today's result quite good?
I am happy.
Just too happy.
Originally, I thought
we'd play one more game with them,
just to satisfy our craving,
since we were bound to lose anyway.
I really thought it was the last game.
If we lost, everyone would give up.
But...
You want to continue?
Ms. Lin, do you think I'm
biting off more than I can chew?
How could I?
If you were really that bad at football,
you wouldn't have been admitted
as sports recruits.
The talent class has been disbanded.
What kind of sports recruits are we now?
Actually, today,
drawing with them
really feels like a dream.
I really love football.
So I don't want it to end.
I know better than anyone else
that we are already in high school.
Those who have what it takes
would have shown it by now.
Football is a game of 11 players.
It's impossible for everyone to be willing
to play along with me like this.
But I...
just can't bring myself to give up.
Ms. Lin,
in this life,
I don't have any chances left.
Fu, stop chatting!
-The bus is here! Let's go!
-Let's go, Fu!
Coming.
Go, go, go!
Hurry up.
Coming!
Why did he go to sleep so early?
I'll thank him another day.
Dream?
I really love football.
So I don't want it to end.
What does that have to do with me?
I knew it.
Wang Fa?
Wang Fa.
Sorry.
I saw your door was unlocked,
so I let myself in.
Miss Landlady,
it's so late.
Is there something you need?
Your floor is leaking water.
Sorry,
I didn't notice.
It's okay,
but please get someone
to fix it as soon as possible.
I didn't scare you, did I?
No.
Holding your breath underwater
must be for seeking inner peace.
I suggest you
try diving. The effect might be better.
It seems you
know a lot about psychology.
It's just a friendly reminder.
After all, I am your landlady.
If anything really happens to you,
it will be very tricky for me.
[Administrative Building]
Director Qian,
I've thought about it.
The football team's draw this time
shows they're actually pretty good.
What they need
is a more professional supervisor.
I think...
the teachers in the P.E. department
are very suitable.
Director,
I can't do it.
Ms. Lin,
the fact that you achieved such a result
the first time you led the team
means you are very competent
-for the position of supervisor.
-Here we go ahain.
You must continue
to work hard in the future.
Director, I really can't do it.
Actually, in the P.E. department,
the other teachers' schedules
are very full.
Mr. Li, that track and field competition
of yours,
is it going to start soon?
Yes, our track and field team
is very busy with training.
The competition will start next month.
Your ball game competition...
Our basketball group
also has a competition next month.
Ball games group is also very busy.
I can't do it.
I don't know anything.
Look at them.
All of them are actually very busy.
Alright,
we are back to square one.
Ms. Lin,
you haven't been at the school for long.
I have to tell you
the truth about some things.
Actually, the competition
for positions in the school
is very fierce.
-He's going to use his trump card again.
-Especially during the probation period.
It mainly depends on your performance.
You see, you are a contract worker,
and you haven't become
a regular employee yet, right?
How can you become
a regular employee then?
You have to complete...
-I was too naive.
-the task assigned by the school leaders
and achieve good results.
I actually believed
that it was just a one-round tour,
just going through the motions.
Now it seems that I have to
take this job whether I want to or not.
That's impossible.
So what counts as achieving good results?
I think
you have to make it out of the preliminaries
and into the next round.
The next round?
But...
they don't even have a coach.
Ms. Lin,
you are absolutely right.
As the team supervisor,
you have the responsibility and obligation
to find a coach for the team.
Me? Find a coach?
Hurry up and do it now.
Ms. Lin,
completing the task assigned to you
by the school leadership
is a very honorable thing.
Where am I supposed to find a coach?
Go for it.
Director Qian,
school is over, so I'm leaving now.
-Okay.
Bye.
Goodbye, Ms. Lin.
This is too hard for me.
[The Second General Assembly
of the Hongjing No. 8 High School Football Team]
The second general sssembly...
I'm melting, bro.
I can't stand it anymore.
What are we doing?
Let's go.
-It stinks.
-Seriously.
-Why did she call us here?
-Who knows?
Hello, Ms. Lin.
Alright, babies.
Sit down.
I'm not a baby.
What kind of baby eats 3 meals a day,
and 5 bowls of rice per meal?
Ms. Lin, please watch your words.
Got it.
My dear ba-
-ttle-tested students.
Find a place to sit.
You are not a baby.
-Sit.
-Baby Lin Lu, let's go.
[The Second General Assembly
of the Hongjing No. 8 High School Football Team]
You should know
why I called you here, right?
We refuse.
That fast?
Won't you...
consider it?
What's there to consider?
In the school's eyes,
we're just a bunch of hooligans.
The school doesn't value
our football team at all.
Why waste time?
A-Actually, it's really rare for us
to have this opportunity.
There's nothing wrong
with continuing to play,
is there?
Right?
Fine, let's give it a try.
What if they abandon us again
after a couple of games?
This time, the school
really wants to rebuild the team
and win back the title
of Football Characteristic Campus.
That's a bit too ambitious.
Yeah, Ms. Lin.
We were just lucky last time
to tie with Ning'an Experimental School.
And the school wants us to rebuild the
Football Characteristic Campus?
I think this task
is too heavy for us.
Besides, we don't even have a coach.
We are trying hard to find a coach
already.
Ms. Lin.
I'm wondering,
is it possible for us
to hire a top-level coach?
Like your elementary school classmate.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
I think that will work.
With a former Nanton coach leading us,
our team would actually have a chance.
He's really got some skills.
But...
can we actually invite him over?
That's Nanton, bro.
How is that possible?
Is it really impossible?
Maybe Ms. Lin isn't capable enough.
I'll try my best.
Alright.
If you can get him to come,
we'll play.
For real?
For real.
Really.
Alright.
I'll try.
Wen Chengye,
why did you trick me?
Let me teach you a lesson.
Don't easily trust others' promises.
You seem very hostile towards me.
I have never offended you, right?
Is that so?
Think again.
Wen Chengye.
Lay a finger on Fu and you'll see.
Seems you've got a new friend.
An idiot.
Who are you calling an idiot?
We just drew with Ning'an.
What's with the "oh"?
What does it matter to me?
Idiots.
A bunch of idiots.
Say that again.
-Come back!
-Qin Ao!
[Director Qian]
Ms. Lin,
did you find a coach?
The principal gave the order.
You must find a way to form the team
and achieve some results.
Good luck. I believe in you.
Asking him shouldn't require money, right?
[Director Qian]
[Contacts]
[New Friends] [I'm Winfred]
[Please wait]
[Permission Settings]
[Processing]
[Slack Superstar]
Mr. Win,
I would like to take the liberty to ask,
shouldn't the water leak problem
be solved?
I found someone.
They will start working tomorrow.
By the way, I have another question.
Would you be willing...
to coach those kids from last time?
No.
I knew it.
No way.
For Grandpa,
I must keep this job.
What should I do?
♪ There's nothing to fear ♪
♪ Because you're with me ♪
♪ The light shimmers ♪
♪ Brilliant as stars ♪
♪ Running towards you ♪
♪ I keep moving fearlessly ♪
♪ Walk side by side ♪
♪ Become ourselves ♪